

www.manpreetdesigner.com

manpreetsinghassi@gmail.com | in /manpreetsinghassi | \$\cup +1 (604) 364 9955 | \$\QQ\$ Vancouver, BC

## About

A UI/UX designer who values collaboration and actively seeks out diverse perspectives to create user-friendly interfaces. With a strong focus on meeting project objectives, approaches tasks with a curious mindset and a meticulous attention to detail, ensuring an intuitive and engaging user experience.

## **Technical Skills**

**Tools** — Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, XD.

**Development** — HTML, CSS, Javascript, Wordpress.

# **Project Experience**

Tourpal Vancouver, BC, Canada (May 2022 - August 2022)

#### UI designer & Front end developer

Tourpal is a web application which provides a curated list of local destinations where the user can choose the local tour guides to get the best possible experience.

- Designed project logo using Adobe Illustrator, inspired from the project goals.
- Provided assistance with the user flow, wireframes, mockups which accelerated overall productivity of the project.
- Created the front end of the web application using HTML and CSS which resulted in positive feedback from users and a successful project outcome.

### **Nexum** Vancouver, BC, Canada (September 2022 - December 2022)

#### **UI/UX** designer

Nexum is a web application solution for education institutes to enhance communication between students and alumni.

- Assisted the other designers with the generation of user flow and wireframes that increased the work efficiency.
- Created a simple and clean design for the website that helped to improve the usability by making it easier for users to navigate.
- Finished a fully functional prototype of the mockups which was used for user testing to improve the user experience.
- Designed the social media assets which were used to promote the application on social media platforms.

### **Stylify** Vancouver, BC, Canada (January 2023 - April 2023)

### **UI/UX** designer

Stylify is a mobile application which helps salons to manage their appointments, keep track of their analytics and create deals.

- Finished user stories and user personas for target audience which were essential to help the team understand target audience needs.
- Assisted lead designer with user flow, wireframes, mockups and prototyping ensuring that the team meets deadlines and produces a high-quality product on time.
- Created social media assets and provided assistance with project proposal which helped to increase the visibility and awareness of the product.

## **Education**

### **Computer Science Engineering**

Chandigarh University Gharuan, Mohali, India August 2016 - May 2020

### Web & Mobile App Design

Vancouver, BC, Canada
January 2022 - April 2023